<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<dedications>
	<dedication>
		<version>0.1.0.0</version>
		<author>James White</author>
		<dedicator>D. Moonfire</dedicator>
		<p>
			Author Intrusion was inspired by a single story: Fast Trip by James
			White. It was something I read almost a decade ago, but the story
			stuck with me not because of the starvation themes or the
			dead-panned logic needed to survive a month-long trip following a
			spaceship accident, but how they survived. In that setting, every
			ship was psychologically tailored to the pilot: things painted in
			the right colors, controls set in the correct place, and even the
			sounds were personalized to the pilot. They were comfortable in
			their cockpit, at ease enough to land a ship. The protagonist,
			Herdman, wasn’t the pilot of the ship about to crash into Mars, but
			he was the only pilot capable of landing it. The story talks about
			his struggles to prepare for a landing, but the crux of the story
			came when he realized he had to change his environment. In the last
			days of their trip, he painted and arranged the cockpit to be closer
			to what he needed, to make him fast enough and capable enough to
			land the ship without killing everyone on board.
		</p>
		<p>
			This program is my attempt to alter my environment. Word processors
			work for a lot of people, but I’m a programmer and a writer. There
			are things that exist in development environments that don’t exist
			in writing programs: a strong preference for keyboard shortcuts,
			introspection and analysis, and navigation. I also want something
			that I can tailor to my own personal flaws, frequently using the
			wrong tense or an overuse of gerunds, that most writing programs
			don’t have. I needed a flexibility to check for one grammar rule
			outside of quotes verses another inside. Or to customize the grammar
			and style guidelines to fit my style instead of a one-size-fits-all
			program that tries to make me conform to one (potentially bland)
			style.
		</p>
		<p>
			In the end, this is an attempt to make my own cockpit. But, I’m also
			going to make it generic enough that it will be a cockpit for other
			writers who have the same physiological quirks as me. It won’t be
			perfect and it won’t work for everyone, but there are others who may
			find that this is a better environment for writing than what they
			had before.
		</p>
	</dedication>
	<dedication>
		<version>0.2.0.0</version>
		<author>Jennifer Roberson</author>
		<dedicator>D. Moonfire</dedicator>
		<p>
			When I was growing up, the Tiger and Del novels by Jennifer Roberson
			were some of my favorite "go to" places to read. I loved the
			world-building but also how she wrote two distinct cultures and
			brought them together, sometimes with disasterous conquences. I
			spent hours reading and re-reading Roberson's novels throughout high
			school.
		</p>
		<p>
			This release was part of both of those. One was trying to write
			using characters from another culture. In specific, characters with
			accented characters. True, Jennifer Roberson didn't really use
			characters with such names, but it was writing stories about other
			cultures that brought up some nasty bugs. The others was how one
			well-meaning attempt turned into a disasterous bug that needed to be
			fixed to keep writing.
		</p>
	</dedication>
	<dedication>
		<version>0.3.0.0</version>
		<author>Madeleine L’Engle</author>
		<dedicator>D. Moonfire</dedicator>
		<p>
			Madeleine L’Engle was the first author I ever wrote a fan letter to.
			It was for a school project and I still remembered the frustration
			of my first grade teacher as I tried to write a letter to someone I
			only saw as a name on the front of the book. The book, on the other
			hand, I remember well. It was "A Wrinkle in Time" and it was the
			first young adult novel I remembered, back when my peers were
			struggling with their chapbooks.
		</p>
		<p>
			I never got a response from that letter, but I still remember
			sending it out. It may have been almost thirty-three years ago, but
			that moment still burns brightly in my memories.
		</p>
		<p>
			Madeleine’s stories gave me a sense of wonderment. The ideas on the
			page were things I never even considered. It was a joy to explore
			her world and characters and settings. I'm sure that the first
			dog-eared book is one of the many things that sent me down a path of
			being a writer.
		</p>
	</dedication>
	<dedication>
		<version>0.4.0.0</version>
		<author>Fredrick Pohl</author>
		<dedicator>D. Moonfire</dedicator>
		<p>
			Fredrick Pohl was one of the writers that got me interested in
			science fiction. His hard science complemented my own technical
			nature, showing a world that was possible to still be strange and
			wonderful while being rooted firmly in reality. One of the most
			influential stories he wrote was a later one, Man Plus, about the
			nature of humanity when it came to serving the greater good. This
			story has resonated with my own goals in life and probably has
			contributed to this program as much as any other influence.
		</p>
		<p>
			Fredrick's longevity is also an inspiration. He never gave up, not
			after almost eight decades of writing. One could hope that I'll be
			writing and programming for half as long.
		</p>
	</dedication>
</dedications>