<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<dedications>
	<dedication>
		<version>0.1.0.0</version>
		<author>James White</author>
		<dedicator>D. Moonfire</dedicator>
		<p>
			Author Intrusion was inspired by a single story: Fast Trip by James
			White. It was something I read almost a decade ago, but the story
			stuck with me not because of the starvation themes or the
			dead-panned logic needed to survive a month-long trip following a
			spaceship accident, but how they survived. In that setting, every
			ship was psychologically tailored to the pilot: things painted in
			the right colors, controls set in the correct place, and even the
			sounds were personalized to the pilot. They were comfortable in
			their cockpit, at ease enough to land a ship. The protagonist,
			Herdman, wasn’t the pilot of the ship about to crash into Mars, but
			he was the only pilot capable of landing it. The story talks about
			his struggles to prepare for a landing, but the crux of the story
			came when he realized he had to change his environment. In the last
			days of their trip, he painted and arranged the cockpit to be closer
			to what he needed, to make him fast enough and capable enough to
			land the ship without killing everyone on board.
		</p>
		<p>
			This program is my attempt to alter my environment. Word processors
			work for a lot of people, but I’m a programmer and a writer. There
			are things that exist in development environments that don’t exist
			in writing programs: a strong preference for keyboard shortcuts,
			introspection and analysis, and navigation. I also want something
			that I can tailor to my own personal flaws, frequently using the
			wrong tense or an overuse of gerunds, that most writing programs
			don’t have. I needed a flexibility to check for one grammar rule
			outside of quotes verses another inside. Or to customize the grammar
			and style guidelines to fit my style instead of a one-size-fits-all
			program that tries to make me conform to one (potentially bland)
			style.
		</p>
		<p>
			In the end, this is an attempt to make my own cockpit. But, I’m also
			going to make it generic enough that it will be a cockpit for other
			writers who have the same physiological quirks as me. It won’t be
			perfect and it won’t work for everyone, but there are others who may
			find that this is a better environment for writing than what they
			had before.
		</p>
	</dedication>
</dedications>